Won’t leave
떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god. -Evil god!
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
I gotta kill her or else What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
I can’t go back to Hell! Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw!
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far,
네가 막 나가면
I’ll slice you up completely!
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo! Must get it back!
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
Never miss a chance Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
To attack her from behind! You’re so mean.
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I’ll never give up.
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you’re off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed…
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can’t leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then,
하지만 그때까진
let’s all have fun together! Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
I'm dying! The "summer" is too hot.
죽겠네! '여름'이라는 건 너무 더워
-Endure it. -No can do.
- 참아 - 아니, 못 참아
-Endure-- -No can do!
- 참아... - 못 참는다고!
-We are aliens and we come in peace. -You're a devil.
- 우리는 외계인이고 평화를 원한다 - 넌 악마다
Why don't you have one of those wind machines in here?
왜 여기 네 집엔 그 바람 기계가 없지?
An air conditioner? We can't afford that.
에어컨? 돈이 없어서 못 사
I bet I could get Medusa to buy us one.
메두사에게 시켜서 한 대 사 오라고 해야지
Don't bother. Just live with the fan.
귀찮게 하지 마 선풍기로 만족해
This lukewarm air is not gonna cut it!
이런 미지근한 바람으론 어림도 없어!
We would have an air conditioner if we weren't with Flex Comix.
플렉스 코믹스와 일하지 않으면 우리도 에어컨이 있었겠지
Huh?
응?
The bigger publishers take good care of their talents.
더 큰 출판사가 재능 관리를 잘하지
I'm totally lost!
하나도 못 알아듣겠어!
I'm out! Gonna go cool down at an electronics shop in Akiba.
나갈 거야! 아키바에 있는 전자제품 가게에서 열을 식혀야지
This...
이건
is hell...
지옥이다
It's so hot!
너무 덥다고!
And humid on top of that!
게다가 축축하고!
Discomfort index is 100, no, more like 2020!
불쾌지수는 100이다 아니, 2020 같아!
I can't believe they're hosting the Olympics here.
여기서 올림픽을 개최한다니 기가 막히다
It's such a scam.
완전 사기야
"Omotenashi," my ass!
손님을 환대해? 웃기고 있네
What's with the dissing? You're gonna get roasted for that.
이 '디스'는 뭐지? 그 대가로 넌 통구이가 될 거다
Shut up. I'll just give up, then.
시끄러워 내가 그냥 포기한다
Fine, I'll make it cooler for you.
좋아 내가 시원하게 해줄게
Really?
정말?
W-What's this?
이... 이게 뭐야?
A punishment. It's also much cooler now, right?
벌이다 이제 훨씬 시원하지?
I'm sorry. I'm really, really sorry.
미안해 내가 정말, 정말 잘못했어
It's cooler all right... It's freezing.
시원해서 좋아... 얼겠어
It's freezing... I'm so cold...
꽁꽁 얼겠어... 너무 추워
Well, that's good isn't it, Jashin-chan?
그거 잘됐네 그렇지, 사신짱?
I won't stand for this!
이건 못 참아!
Yurine, you're out of your mind.
유리네, 넌 돌았어
Then don't act like a brat.
그럼 버릇없이 굴지 마
If it's come to this, I better summon "it" from hell.
그렇다면 지옥에서 '그거'나 불러야지
"It"?
"그거?"
Who is this?
이건 누구지?
Kori-chan, an Ice Devil.
코오리짱, 얼음 악마야
Kori-chan?
"코오리짱?"
Funny-looking face.
웃기게 생겼다
Kori-chan can cool a room just by being there.
코오리짱은 있는 것만으로도 방을 차갑게 할 수 있어
-Whoa, it really is cooler in here. -And check this out!
- 정말 여기가 서늘해졌네 - 이것도 봐!
Instant shaved ice.
즉석 빙수다
Impressive.
굉장하다
So, which flavor?
어떤 맛으로 줄까?
Which?
"어떤 맛?"
Strawberry or lemon?
딸기 맛? 아니면 레몬 맛?
Then lemon--
그럼 레몬...
Kori-chan's blood is strawberry
코오리짱의 피는 딸기고
-and her urine is lemon flavor! -I'll take strawberry.
- 오줌은 레몬 맛이야! - 딸기로 할게
It really is strawberry syrup.
정말 딸기 시럽이다
I eat hot foods in the summer to intensify the heat!
난 여름에 뜨거운 음식을 먹어 열을 강화한다!
Ah! It burns!
아! 탄다!
A cool room and shaved ice. So convenient.
시원한 방에서 빙수를 먹으니, 너무 편하다
Very much so.
정말 그렇다
But it doesn't just end there.
하지만 이게 다가 아니야
Kori-chan, do that thing you do.
코오리짱, 너 그거 해봐
You don't want to right now?
지금은 하기 싫다고?
Who do you think you are?
네 주제를 알아야지
A low-class devil like you must obey me.
너 같은 하급 악마는 내게 순종하는 거다
Just do what I asked. Now!
내가 하라는 대로 해 당장!
Easy there, Jashin-chan.
진정해, 사신짱
-Snow...? -Are you impressed or what?
- 눈...? - 감동한 거 맞니?
Low-class devils only exist to entertain us!
하급 악마는 오직 우리를 모시기 위해 존재하는 거야!
You must be honored to serve a high-class devil like me.
나 같은 상급 악마를 모시는 걸 영광으로 알아야지
The snow's getting heavy.
눈이 점점 세진다
Kori-chan, you can stop now.
코오리짱, 이제 멈춰
That's enough!
그만하라고!
Stop right now, damn it!
당장 멈춰, 젠장!
Don't push your luck. I'm done with you, so go home!
요행을 바라지 마 됐으니까, 이제 집에 가
Jashin-chan, watch your mouth. You're being cruel.
사신짱, 말조심해 넌 너무 잔인해
I am not!
아니야!
This is what you get for disobeying me!
내게 복종하지 않은 대가다
Jashin-chan Cho--!
사신짱, 썰...!
Let me explain.
제가 설명하죠
Jashin-chan is relentless to smaller and weaker low-class devils.
작고 약한 하급 악마에게 사신짱은 무자비하게 대합니다
Chop!
썰기!
Let go.
이것 놔
You froze me.
네가 나를 얼렸어?
You stupid brat!
이 멍청하고 버릇없는 것!
I’m glad you were able to cool off.
열을 식혀서 다행이다
Can she regenerate?
다시 살아나는 거지?
How humiliating.
정말 창피하다
You deserved it.
넌 당할 만했어
WHAT WAS ORIGINALLY CALLED "JASHIN-CHAN"
'원래는 '사신짱'이라고 불렸다'
SUZURAN SHOPPING DISTRICT
'스즈란 쇼핑 거리'
I'm s-starving.
배고파
Angels are immortal, but...
천사는 죽지 않지만...
humans are heartless.
인간은 몰인정하다
It's obvious that I'm not okay.
내가 도움이 필요한 걸 분명히 알 거야
My Lord.
신이시여
Humans are completely corrupt now.
인간은 이제 완전히 부패했습니다
Final judgment day
최후 심판의 날이
might be coming in the near future.
곧 다가올 것이다
An a-angel?
처, 천사?
Pekola, are you okay?
페코라, 너 괜찮니?
The witch...
마녀...
Enter Bondy from the back of Kanda Used Bookstore.
본디의 입구는 간다 중고서점 뒤편에 있습니다
Never enter from the bookstore.
서점을 통해서 들어가지 마세요
The potato's tasty.
감자가 맛있다
But, why do they serve potatoes at a curry shop?
하지만 카레 가게에서 감자를 왜 주는 거지?
Eat or talk, just choose one.
먹든 말하든 하나만 해
Why do they serve potatoes?
왜 감자를 주는 거야?
Who knows?
나도 몰라
Thank you for waiting.
기다려 주셔서 고맙습니다
Dig in, curry's best when it's still hot.
먹어, 카레는 뜨거울 때 먹어야 맛있어
Thank you.
고마워
Delicious.
맛있다
May I have another serving?
한 그릇 더 먹어도 돼?
Sure, I'll take it from Jashin-chan's food budget.
응, 사신짱의 식비 예산에서 뺄 거야
One more, please!
하나 더 부탁합니다
Right away.
바로 나갑니다
It's not angel-like of you to wander around starving.
네가 굶주린 채 돌아다니면 천사 같지 않아
It's very human.
매우 인간 같아
Without my halo,
후광이 없으면
I'm no different than a feeble human.
난 약한 인간과 똑같아
With my halo, I can work miracles.
후광이 있으면 기적을 만들 수 있지
Transforming rock into bread, water into wine.
돌을 빵으로 물을 와인으로 만들 수 있어
Excuse me, I'm looking for someone.
실례합니다 사람을 찾고 있어요
Do you know if Jashin-chan lives around here?
혹시 사신짱이 이 근처에 살고 있나요?
Jashin-chan?
사신짱?
I was sent by my mother from hell
우리 엄마가 절 지옥에서 보냈는데
to search for Jashin-chan.
사신짱을 찾으래요
JINBOCHO POLICE
'진보초 경찰'
Why don't you stay with us for about three days?
우리하고 여기에 한 3일 정도 있을래?
Yeah, you're suspicious.
그래, 넌 의심스러워
-But, Jashin-chan-- -Sure, sure.
- 하지만, 사신짱... - 그래, 그래
Did you eat enough?
충분히 먹었어?
Yup, thank you so--
응, 정말 고마...
Thanking a witch means I'm betraying God!
마녀에게 감사하는 건 신을 배신하는 거다!
But, she treated me and I even got seconds!
하지만 내게 밥을 사줬어 난 2인분이나 먹었지!
-I've been sinning all this time! -May I have another serving?
- 계속 죄를 지은 거야 - 한 그릇 더 먹어도 돼?
You talk to yourself too much.
혼잣말을 너무 많이 한다
But it's true, the witch saved my life.
하지만 마녀가 날 살린 건 사실이다
Yurine Hanazono.
하나조노 유리네
I've no choice but to thank you.
난 너에게 고마워할 수밖에 없어
But, I still haven't given up on eliminating you and the devils.
하지만 너와 악마를 없애는 걸 아직 포기하지 않았어
Just wait. When I find my halo, and get my powers back,
기다려, 내가 후광을 찾아 내 힘을 되찾으면
I'll eliminate you all!
너희 모두를 제거할 거다!
I hope you find your halo soon.
네 후광을 빨리 찾기 바라
Idiot, weren't you listening to what I just said?
바보야, 내가 뭐라고 했는지 안 들었어?
I get so confused when I'm with you. I'm going home!
너하고 있으면 너무 헷갈려 집에 갈래!
Bless her heart.
쟤 마음에 축복이 있기를
My Lord, what should I do?
신이시여, 어떻게 해야 하죠?
Should I consider her my neighbor,
쟤는 마녀인데도
even though she’s a witch?
이웃으로 여겨야 하나요?
This world is full of contradictions!
이 세계는 온통 모순덩어리다!
My Lord, why did they serve potatoes?
신이시여, 왜 그들은 감자를 줬나요?
Jashin-chan?
사신짱?
100% BEEF
'100% 쇠고기'
We're here!
우리 왔어!
Jashin-chan?
사신짱?
She invited us and she's not even here.
우리를 초대해놓고 집에 없네
Maybe...
아마
She's in here.
여기 있을 거야
Nope.
없다
I usually find her hiding in here.
늘 여기 숨은 걸 찾았어
I'm right here!
난 바로 여기 있지
Trumped you there!
내가 이겼다!
Medusa's like,
메두사가 뭐랬지?
"I usually find her hiding in here."
"늘 여기 숨은 걸 찾았어"?
Dumbass!
멍청이야! 왜 내가 같은 곳에 계속 숨겠니? 바보야
I-I'll check under the floors next time.
다음엔 마루 밑을 볼게
But, why were you hiding at all?
하지만 넌 대체 왜 숨는 거야?
Good question! Let me tell you...
좋은 질문이다 내가 말해 주지...
I know! You were testing to see if it was a good place to hide
알았다! 넌 유리네를 기습 공격할 때 숨기 좋은 장소를
for when you go for a surprise attack on Yurine!
알아내려고 실험하는구나?
Oh?
어?
How'd you know?
네가 어떻게 알지?
Save yourself the effort. You'll fail again.
괜히 힘 빼지 마 넌 또 실패할 거야
-Hey, Minos. -Yeah?
- 얘, 미노스 - 응?
Convince her to give up on killing Yurine.
유리네를 죽이는 거 그만두라고 해줘
No! I'll never give up!
안 돼! 난 절대 포기 안 해!
Off you go. The experiment's over.
너희는 가 실험은 끝났어
Out you go.
다들 나가
Any minute now...
곧 올 시간이다...
I'm back.
나 왔어
I'm hungry. The trident was on sale today for half off so I bought it.
배고파, 삼지창을 할인해서 반값에 샀어
-Looks like she's not even here. -What? A trident?
- 여기도 없는 것 같네 - 뭐? 삼지창?
There!
여기다!
That's a good place to store it for now.
당분간 여기에 둬야겠다
Why would you stab a trident through the floor?
왜 삼지창으로 마루를 찍어서 뚫는 거야?
She seems clueless.
전혀 모르는 것 같아
But who knows.
하지만 모르지
She might already know I'm in here.
내가 여기 있는 걸 이미 알지도 몰라
Let me check.
확인해야지
All right. She really doesn't know.
좋아 쟤는 정말 모르는군
I'll throw this at her just for fun.
이걸 던지면 재밌겠다
Ouch.
아야!
An avocado...?
아보카도...?
I'll eat it later.
나중에 먹어야지
She's clueless!
전혀 모른다!
She's gonna eat it later? What an idiot.
그걸 나중에 먹는다고? 정말 바보군
At this rate, I could probably go for it...
그렇다면 시도해야지
I'll sneak up behind her and use this.
살금살금 뒤에서 다가가서 이걸 쓸 거야
This is the end.
이거로 끝이다
Goodbye, Yurine!
잘 가라, 유리네!
YURINE
'유리네'
H-Hey there.
아, 안녕
I see what's going on.
어떻게 된 건지 알겠군
I didn't expect to be able to test out the trident so soon.
난 이렇게 빨리 삼지창을 써보게 될지 몰랐다
T-Trident happy?
사, 삼지창 좋지?
Let's "try."
한번 써보자
Well, I knew that was coming.
저렇게 될 줄 알았어
I did my part, I warned her.
경고했으니까 내 할 일은 한 거야
What is that?
그건 뭐야?
A tomahawk, it was 80 percent off at the weapon shop.
도끼야, 무기 상점에서 80% 할인해서 샀어
Hello, Jashin-chan?
여보세요, 사신짱?
Medusa? Come here now!
메두사? 지금 이리 와!
-W-Why? -I'll tell you later!
- 왜? - 나중에 얘기할게
Jashin-chan?
사신짱?
Excuse me!
실례합니다!
Your voice is adorable!
당신 목소리가 너무 좋군요
You sound exactly like Miyutan!
미유탄 목소리와 똑같아요!
What's with this bag?
이 봉투는 뭐죠?
N-No! Not my face!
내, 내 얼굴은 안 돼요!
Don't worry! With a cute voice like yours,
걱정하지 마요! 이렇게 목소리가 예쁘면
you'll look cute even if you're not all that!
별로라고 해도 귀여울 거예요
That's why I told you to stop.
그래서 그만두라고 했잖아요
I gotta get to Jashin-chan now!
지금 사신짱에게 가야 해
Here you go.
마셔
Thank you.
고마워
Tokyo's a dense city.
도쿄엔 사람이 많아
I wouldn't worry about fossilizing one guy.
남자 한 명이 돌이 된다고 신경 쓰지 않을 거야
Anyway, why isn't she here when she invited you?
그런데 널 오라고 해놓고 그 애는 어디 간 거지?
Jashin-chan has no respect.
사신짱은 예의가 없어
I'm pretty used to it.
늘 그래서 익숙해
Delicious.
맛있다
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
Does she always treat you this bad?
사신짱이 널 항상 하찮게 취급하니 ?
What? Oh no, not really.
뭐? 아니, 그렇진 않아
Really? So, was she always like this?
정말? 그러니까 그 애가 늘 이랬다는 거지?
Well, let's see...
그러니까, 보자...
When we attended Hell Elementary...
우리가 지옥 초등학교에 다닐 때
Jashin-chan acted out
사신짱이 말썽부리다가
and knocked down a statue in the courtyard.
정원에 있던 동상을 깨뜨렸어
Who broke the gargoyle statue?
누가 괴물 석상을 깨뜨렸지?
She hasn't changed a bit.
전혀 변하지 않았군
But, when Jashin-chan was bullying a weak devil...
하지만 사신짱이 약한 악마를 괴롭힐 땐...
Dumb goblin, you can't score higher than me!
멍청한 도깨비야 나보다 높은 점수를 받겠다고?
Stop it, Jashin-chan!
하지 마, 사신짱
You're dumb and stupid!
넌 멍청한 바보야!
What did my son do to you?
내 아들이 네게 무슨 잘못을 했지?
I said no, but Medusa forced me!
전 싫다고 했는데 메두사가 하라고 했어요
No, I didn't!
아니에요, 안 그랬어요
Good times.
좋은 때였어
What part?
어떤 부분이?
Oh, yeah, when she fell in a trap...
그리고 그 애가 함정에 빠졌을 땐...
All right.
좋아
-See ya! -Wait! Don't leave me in here!
- 잘 있어 - 기다려, 날 두고 가지 마!
They finally found me after three days.
사람들이 3일 후에 날 찾아냈어
Another time...
또 한 번은...
-Do anything to her but let me go. -No!
- 얘를 맘대로 하고 나는 보내줘요 - 안 돼!
Those were the days.
그럴 때도 있었어
-Another time! -Enough.
- 또 있어! - 됐다
You've gone through too much.
넌 너무 많이 당했어
Really?
정말?
I guess as devils,
내 생각에 악마는
it doesn't matter if you're mean and cunning.
못되고 교활해도 상관없는 것 같아
Hey there! I'm a meanie!
안녕! 난 심술 덩어리야!
Why are you still her friend even though she betrays you all the time?
넌 늘 배신당하면서 왜 아직도 그 애와 친구를 하니?
Are you an "M"?
너 'M'이니?
In any case, Jashin-chan's still trash.
아무튼 사신짱은 여전히 쓰레기야
Actually, she can be pretty cute at times.
그래도 가끔 아주 귀여워
Whenever she's in trouble,
그 애가 곤경에 처할 때는
she relies on me the most!
내게 가장 많이 의지해!
UNDERWORLD
'저승세계'
It's just a devilish perspective!
그건 단지 악마의 관점이지!
Damn it!
젠장!
Medusa!
메두사!
Wait for me!
기다려
Don't abandon me!
날 버리지 마!
You're the only one I could count on!
난 너밖에 믿을 사람이 없어!
Forgive me for everything I've done to you.
내가 너에게 저지른 모든 걸 용서해줘
I know you like me, Medusa!
넌 날 좋아하잖아, 메두사!
When I see her so vulnerable...
그 애가 그렇게 약한 모습을 보일 땐
She makes me think
이런 생각을 하게 돼
she can't live without me, that I need to be there for her.
사신짱은 나 없이 못 사니까 내가 곁에 있어 줘야 한다고
Careful, don't let any losers take advantage of you.
조심해, 어떤 루저에게도 이용당하지 마라
O-Okay, I'll be careful.
그래, 조심할게
I'm back!
나 왔어!
She's home.
집에 왔다
Don't go out when you invite Medusa over.
메두사를 초대해놓고 밖에 나가지 마
She doesn't mind.
얘는 괜찮아
Medusa's lower in class so I make her wait.
메두사는 나보다 하급이라 기다리게 하는 거야
Welcome back, Jashin-chan. Why did you call me?
돌아온 걸 환영해, 사신짱 왜 날 불렀어?
This is all the money I have.
내가 가진 건 이 돈이 전부야
10,000 YEN
'1만엔'
-Idiot! Not in front of Yurine. -S-Sorry.
- 바보야! 유리네가 있잖아! - 미, 미안해
I never asked you for money.
난 너한테 돈 달라고 한 적 없어
But, if you say so, I'll happily accept the cash.
하지만 네가 원한다면 기꺼이 그 돈을 받지
Then what did you want me for?
그렇다면 내가 어떻게 해줘야 해?
If it's illegal in hell,
지옥에서 불법인 거라면
I can't help you.
난 널 도울 수 없어
We'll handle that later. I called you for this today.
그건 나중에 처리하자 오늘은 이것 때문에 불렀어
I won you this at an arcade in Ikebukuro.
이케부쿠로 오락실에서 너 주려고 이걸 땄어
You said it was cute last time.
저번에 네가 예쁘다고 했지?
The panda human doll.
판다 인간 인형이다
Jashin-chan, you remembered!
사신짱, 기억하고 있었네?
I won it using your money, Medusa.
네 돈을 써서 이걸 땄다, 메두사
Here you go.
받아
Thanks so much, Jashin-chan!
정말 고마워, 사신짱!
Don't hug me! Who do you think you are?
날 안지 마! 네 주제를 알아야지
I only did it because it benefits me.
내게 이익이니까 그걸 가져온 것뿐이다
It means nothing more than that.
그것 말고 아무 의미도 없어
But, I'm still happy!
하지만, 그래도 난 행복해
Stop it! Don't hug me!
하지 마! 날 안지 말라고!
It looks like a happy ending.
해피엔딩처럼 보이는군
But, it's all doomed.
하지만 불행해질 거다
This looks familiar.
많이 본 광경 같아
Medusa!
메두사!
I've seen this before.
전에도 이걸 봤지
Dropkick on her! Yeah her! I’ll take you down again!
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you! Love doesn’t exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick! An Angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death!
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It’s a love and hate relationship,
이건 애증 관계야
can’t leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star!
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and DIE!
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don’t stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let’s go! Dream on! No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We’re a happy family La la la
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you!!
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I’m home! Welcome back, it’s hot pot tonight!
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone! Let’s enjoy this meal!
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, Wakeup!
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
Winter has come. The streets are filled with Christmas spirit.
겨울이 왔다, 거리는 크리스마스 분위기로 가득 찼다
Away from the bustle of the city, a poor girl cries.
부산한 도시와 떨어진 곳에서 한 불쌍한 소녀가 운다
Dropkick on My Devil! We'll camel clutch your heart in the next episode too!
사신짱 드롭킥! 다음 화에서도 여러분 마음에 카멜 클러치를 겁니다!